piphut.com 2012-05-24

# Privacy Policy – PipHut Forex Community « « PipHut.com PipHut.com

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Your privacy is very important to us.  At Piphut.com, LLC (“Piphut”), we want to make your experience with us satisfying and safe.

This Privacy Policy outlines the types of information we gather from your use of the product, how we use it, with whom we might share it, the means by which we keep it secure, and the choices you have about the information you choose to share with us.

If you have any questions about the privacy practices of Piphut or this Privacy Policy, please contact us.

**1.            PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

The types of personal information we collect depend on the product or service you receive from us. This information may include, but is not limited to:

•             Your Name, phone number, physical and e-mail address;

•             Your Credit Card number;

•             Your Account Information, such as account balances and trading activity; and

•             Your Demographic Information, such as your age, income range, investment preferences, etc.

**2.             PERSONAL INFORMATION WHY WE COLLECT IT**

Piphut may collect certain personal information to provide you with certain information such as trading and investment information, trading and research tools, to perform marketing and research related activities, to supply other administrative services, and to respond to inquiries. In addition we may from time to time review your usage of the site to be able to better provide you with information about products or services that we believe may be interest to you.

**3.             PERSONAL INFORMATION HOW WE COLLECT IT**

The personal information we collect may be captured from a variety of sources. These sources include, but are not limited to:

•             Voluntary submissions (e.g., responses to surveys, requests for information on our products or those of our advertisers or marketing partners);

•             Registrations/Applications to receive products or services; and

•             Reviews of site usage patterns.

**4.             USE AND ACCESS OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH OTHERS**

As a general rule, Piphut will not make the personal information gathered using Piphut available to anyone outside of Piphut and its affiliates, except as instructed by you or where required to comply with law. Please note, however, that there are several exceptions to this policy.

First, if we use service providers, these service providers may have access to your personal information to perform contractually specified services on behalf of Piphut or you.  Second, if you indicate that you are interested in receiving information about a particular third party’s products/services, or you opt to receive certain products or services through Piphut, we may provide your personal information to that third party for purposes of fulfilling your request(s). With respect to service provider, Piphut may contractually require that all personal information be kept confidential. Additionally, Piphut takes reasonable steps to ensure that third parties receiving information about you at your request maintain the confidentially of that information.

**5.             LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**

Piphut may provide links to one or more other websites. We encourage you to read their individual privacy policies before providing any of your personal information to them.

**6.             PROTECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Piphut puts reasonable security measures in place to protect against unauthorized access to, or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of personal information. These measures include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

Piphut may operate secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies may be periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided.

**7.             USE OF COOKIES **

Piphut may, in its sole discretion, use cookies to set users’ preferences, gather basic tracking information (such as login and password), date, time of visit and preferences, and monitor the presentation of our site. This information allows us to personalize the user experience and to improve the quality of our site navigation. Cookies do not reveal the identity of the individual user but only identify the computer utilized by that user.

Please note that advertisers on our site may also deploy cookies and other technology to gather users’ basic site usage information (such as pages visited or frequency of visits) to measure and improve the effectiveness of their advertising. For more information regarding Advertisers’ practices, including how to opt-out of their cookie tracking, please visit the advertisers’ privacy policies.

**8.             ACCURACY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

You are responsible for periodically checking to ensure that your personal information included in site is updated and correct.

**9.             HOW TO UPDATE PERSONAL INFORMATION**

If you desire to update any personal information, you may do so by accessing Piphut.

**10.          YOUR CONSENT**

By using the Piphut, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information and any related information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy.

**11.          CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY**

Piphut reserves the right to change this policy at any time by distributing and/or posting a new privacy policy without notice. We encourage you to review our privacy policy on a regular basis so that you will be aware of any changes to it.

If you have further questions about our privacy practices, please contact us.
